# anna dolan

## **Software Developer**

phone:

720.272.0069

email:

anna.dolan@gmail.com

personal site:

www.anna-dolan.com

github:

https://github.com/annadolan

As a software developer with a background in real estate, I am skilled in time management and organization, and I have a great deal of experience in a client-facing environment. My technical skills and interests are suited for a broad range of industries, and I hope to work alongside, and learn from, a team of well-rounded developers.

#### Skills

Languages/Frameworks: Ruby, Rails, HTML/CSS, ActiveRecord Systems/practices: Git, OAuth, Capybara, RSpec, Bootstrap, PostgreSQL

### **Projects**

Pinspiration (group project)

https://github.com/annadolan/pinspiration

https://the-real-pinspiration.herokuapp.com/

Pinterest clone that also serves a JSON API for comments on pins.

Tech Stack: Rails, PostgreSQL, jQuery, Masonry (grid layout)

Root & Branch (group project)

https://github.com/annadolan/root and branch

http://root-and-branch.herokuapp.com/

Mock web store written in Rails, complete with user authentication and admin authorization and a functioning cart and checkout.

Tech Stack: Rails, PostgreSQL, Bootstrap

Rales Engine (pair project)

https://github.com/annadolan/rails\_engine

Versioned JSON API that uses ActiveRecord to perform complex business intelligence with sales data.

Tech Stack: Rails, PostgreSQL

## Recent Experience

Student, Turing School of Software and Design; Denver, CO — 2016-present Backend Engineering Student

Assistant Investment Manager, Triton Properties; Denver, CO - 2011-2016 Assisted in managing more than 250 apartment units in 9 buildings

Keyholder, American Apparel, Denver, CO — 2010-2011 Assisted in daily operations, sales, and training.

#### Education

Turing School of Software and Design; Denver, CO Backend Engineering

University of Colorado Denver; Denver, CO

BA Fine Arts, Drawing emphasis